Guide to the Thomas Parran Papers, 1892-1968 UA.90.F14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Publications - Correspondence, Travel Expenses, Vouchers, 1926-1944; IV.
  - Parran - insurance (Box 27, Folder 265)
  - Lasker Award Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 266)
  - Distinguished Service Medal, September 3, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 267)
  - Parran - property, rental (Box 28, Folder 268)
  - Fan Letters - Dr. Thomas Parran (Box 28, Folder 269)
  - Requests for photographs (Box 28, Folder 270)
- Personal Correspondence Files - Parran, V.
  - Publications - general, personal correspondence files (Box 28, Folder 271)
  - Publications, acknowledgements (Box 28, Folder 272)
  - Fortune (Box 28, Folder 273)
  - Future (Box 28, Folder 274)
  - Ladies Home Journal (Box 28, Folder 275)
  - Life (Box 29, Folder 276)
  - J.B. Lippincott Co. (Box 29, Folder 277)
  - The MacMillan Co. (Box 29, Folder 278)
  - Modern Hospital Publishing Co. (Box 29, Folder 279)
  - Parents Magazine (Box 29, Folder 280)
  - Pictorial Statistics, Inc. (Box 29, Folder 281)
  - The Readers Digest (Box 29, Folder 282)
  - Reynal Hitchcock (Box 29, Folder 283)
  - Survey Associates, Inc. (Box 29, Folder 284)
  - Time (Box 29, Folder 285)
  - Parran - Income Tax (Box 29, Folder 286)
  - Tax notices to administrator, Federal Security Agency (Box 29, Folder 287)
  - Travel Expenses, 1936-1940, 1941-1944 (Box 29, Folder 288-289)
  - Travel expenses, 1945-1948 (Box 29, Folder 290)
- Addresses and Meetings, VI.
  - Urban vs. Rural Health Service. American Farm Bureau Federation, State of Illinois, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 291)
  - Smallpox Outbreaks at Poteau, Oklahoma, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 292)
  - Local Health Service, Springfield, IL. Anniversary celebration of the founding of the Diagnostic Laboratories, by the State Dept. of Public Health, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 293)
  - Scarlet Fever. Newer Knowledge of, Illinois Health News, November 2, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 294)
  - Physician and Public Health, District Medical Society, Turin Lakes, Iowa, January 22, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 295)
  - Illinois Health News, February, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 296)
  - Science of Public Health - Actual and Potential Accomplishments, Illinois Academy of Science, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 297)
  - County Health Dept. - rural areas. Illinois Farmers Institute, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 298)
  - The Need for Rural Public Health Work, May 7, 1925, Springfield, Ill., Aesculapian Medical, Society of Wabash Valley (Box 30, Folder 299)
  - Rural and Urban Health Work, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 300)
  - The State of Medicine, December 3, Springfield, Ill. Sangamon County Medical Society and State Health Officers, 1926 (Box 30, Folder 301)
  - Public Health Organization of Denmark, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 302)
  - Milk and Milk Products as a factor in the causation of outbreaks of a disease in the United States, Further studies on the importance of (Parran and Armstrong), 1927 (Box 30, Folder 303)
  - Is Medical Science Taking Advantage of Its Opportunities, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 304)
  - Practice of Preventive Medicine, May 31, Moline, Ill. Illinois Medical Society meeting, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 305)
  - Symposium on Research in Syphilis, Oct. 15, Chicago, (Parran, Moore, Brown, Snow), 1928 (Box 30, Folder 306)
  - Tabes and General Paralysis in the U.S. - frequency in later years - treatment malaria, (Parran and Clark), 1928 (Box 30, Folder 307)
  - Extent of Problem of Gonorrhea and Syphilis in the United States, New York City, National Conference of Social Work (Parran and Usilton), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 308)
  - Treatment of Syphilis in its Relation to Prevention, Portland, OR - American Medical Association, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 309)
  - Unsolved Problems in Syphilis, Miami, Fla. American Society for Tropical Medicine, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 310)
  - Career Position - Making the Office of a Health commissioner, New York City, New York Health Conference (Box 30, Folder 311)
  - Federation of Women's Clubs, Springfield, IL., 1930 (Box 30, Folder 312)
  - Public Health Work - Future. Women's Democratic News, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 313)
  - Tuberculosis Sanatorio and General, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 314)
  - Laboratory Service, Rochester, N.Y., New York State Association of Public Health Labs, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 315)
  - Public Health Activities conducted by Women's Clubs Federation of Illinois - Springfield, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 316)
  - Organization and Activities of State Dept. of Health, Ithaca, N.Y., State College of Agriculture, Cornell, July 3, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 317)
  - Cutaneous Mucosal, Relapse Early Syphilis its Differentation from Reinfection, Copenhagen - International Congress of Dermatology and Syphilology. Reprints (Parran, Stokes, Cole, Moore, O'Leary, Wile), Aug. 5-9, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 318)
  - Typhoid Fever - Relation of in Public Water Supplies in N.Y. State, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 319)
  - Trends in Health Conservation. Louisville, KY., Southern Medical Association, Nov. 12, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 320)
  - Venereal Disease Control. Published in the Public Health Nurse New York City, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 321)
  - Health Work in Municipalities, Schenectady, N.Y. Bureau of Municipal Research and the Mayors' Conference of the State of New York, March 13, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 322)
  - State and Provincial Health Conference, Washington D.C., April 27-30, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 323)
  - Oral Hygiene in Public Health Programs, New York City, Dental Society of the State of New York, May 12, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 324)
  - Health Program. Philadelphia, American Medical Association, June 11, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 325)
  - Family Doctor and the School Girl, Saturday Evening Post, Sept. 24, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 326)
  - New York State Health Program, Lake Placid, New York Federation of Women's Clubs, Nov. 9, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 327)
  - Eradication of Syphilis as a Practical Public Health Objective (DeLamor Lecture), Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, March 3, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 328)
  - Syphilis from the Epidemiologist's - Montreal, American Public Health Association, Sept. 17, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 329)
  - Outstanding Public Health Problems; Their Challenge to the Women, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 330)
  - State Program for Oral Hygiene, New York City, May, 1932. New York State Dental Society Dental Cosmos contains article (Box 31, Folder 331)
  - Milk - Remediable Defects in City Milk Control. Buffalo, State Conference of Mayors, June 7, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 332)
  - Syracuse Centennial - Founding of City Health Dept. Syracuse, June 20, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 333-334)
  - Syphilis Control Among Rural Negroes; report of an investigation made for the Julius Rosenwald Fund, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 335)
  - Public Health; A Sound Investment, New York City Radio Broadcast. New York Academy of Medicine, Sept. 19, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 336)
  - Syphilis as a Public Health Problem, Chicago, Institute of Medicine, Oct. 31, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 337)
  - Costs of Medical Care; The Public Welfare Law; Junior Leagues; The Infectivity of Syphilis; A condensed statement of the whole syphilis problem, prepared by Dr. Parran, 1930-1933 (Box 31, Folder 338)
  - Venereal Disease Control, March, New York Academy of Medicine, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 339)
  - Health Aspects of Emergency Relief Work. Buffalo, Social Workers Club, March 23, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 340)
  - Social Hygiene, Syracuse. Onondaga Health Association, March 24, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 341)
  - Medical Care and Public Health - Scholia Club, New York City. Columbia University, Teacher's College (Box 31, Folder 342)
  - The Health of the State - New York City, Medical Society of the State of New York, April 5, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 343)
  - What the Community Should Know About the Health of the State - New York City, Medical Society, April 5, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 344)
  - Public Medical Care in New York State - correspondence re, reprints, news releases. Milwaukee. American Medical Association, June 15, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 345)
  - Common Interests Between the Control of Tuberculosis and Syphilis, New York City, Hospital Social Service Association, June 1933 (Box 32, Folder 346)
  - The Economic Aspects of Public Health and Milk Controls Syracuse, New York State Sanitary Officers Association and the School Physicians of the State of New York, Sept. 27, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 347)
  - Milk Arrives as a Public Utility, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 348)
  - Qualifications and Training of Local Health Officers Indianapolis, American Public Health Association, Oct. 10, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 349)
  - Today's Code for Child Health - Rochester, New York State Nurses' Association, Oct. 17, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 350)
  - Relationship of State Department of Health to Medical Profession, Geneva, N.Y. Geneva Academy of Medicine, Oct. 19, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 351)
  - State Adventures in Milk Control, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 352)
  - Dedication of Greene County Hospital. Catskill, N.Y., 1933 (Box 32, Folder 353)
  - Milk and Health. Syracuse, New York State Farm Bureau Federation, November 9, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 354)
  - Milk Control and Public Health. Editorial, American Journal of Public Health, November 21, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 355)
  - Congenital Syphilis - Washington D.C., Medical Society of the District of Columbia, January 10, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 356)
  - New Deal in Public Health. Elmira, N.Y., Visiting Nurse and Tuberculosis Association, January 17, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 357)
  - Care for the Physically Handicapped - Albany, New York State Crippled Children's Association, January 26, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 358)
  - Local Health Problems that Must Be Solved - Albany, New York State Conference of Mayors, January 27, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 359)
  - Health Services of Tomorrow - Reprints, correspondence in re, news releases. Philadelphia. American Academy of Political and Social Science and College of Physicians of Philadelphia, February 7, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 360)
  - Problems of Interest to the Women of the State - Ithaca, New York State College of Home Economics (Box 32, Folder 361)
  - Next Steps in Milk Control - Ithaca, Agricultural Economics Section of Home and Farm Week, Feb. 15, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 362)
  - Diphtheria Immunization, Broadcast, Albany, April 18, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 363)
  - A New Deal in Public Health - Middletown, N.Y., New York State Committee on Tuberculosis and Public Health, April 19, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 364)
  - Public Health of Tomorrow - New York City, National Tuberculosis Association, April 20, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 365)
  - City of Schenectady National Health Conservation Contest, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 366)
  - Why Our Lack of Progress in Preventing Maternal Deaths New York City, Maternity Center Association, May 10, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 367)
  - Medicine and the Young Practitioner - New York City, Cornell University Medical College (Box 33, Folder 368)
  - Reorganization of County Government. Are We Getting Our Money's Worth - Geneva, N.Y. League of Women Voters, June 20, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 369)
  - Relation of the Retail Price of Milk to Production Costs - Pasadena, CA, American Public Health Association, Sept. 3, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 370)
  - Social Menace of Syphilis - Allegheny, N.Y., Council of Social Agencies, Sept. 13, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 371)
  - Infant and Maternal Mortality - Hornell, N.Y., Conference of Health Officers and Steuben County Medical Society, Sept. 14, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 372)
  - Starvation in a Land of Plenty - Rochester, Rochester and Monroe County Tuberculosis and Health Association, Sept. 26, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 373)
  - Drink More Milk - And Why - Buffalo, Civic Health Council, Inc., Sept. 27, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 374)
  - Health Needs Essential in Child Welfare - Albany, New York State Association of Child Welfare, October 16, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 375)
  - Making Public Health Nursing More Productive - Buffalo, New York State Nurses' Association, October 17, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 376)
  - Venereal Disease Control - White Plains, N.Y., American Red Cross, Oct. 18, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 377)
  - Medicine in a Changing World - Forest Hills, L.I, Queens County Medical Society (Box 33, Folder 378)
  - Public Health Needs, New York City. Reprints and news releases of radio address not given. National Advisory Council on Radio in Education, November 19, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 379-380)
  - Public Health Needs, New York City. Reprints and news releases of radio address not given. National Advisory Council on Radio in Education, November 19, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 381)
  - Common Objectives for the Common Good - Rochester. New York State Teacher's Association, November 2, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 382)
  - Health and Medical Relief in New York State, Asbury, N.J. New Jersey Health and Sanitary Association, November 16, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 383)
  - What Treatment in Early Syphilis Accomplishes, Reprint No. 49 Venereal Disease Information (Parran, Moore, Stokes, Cole, etc.), November, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - Responsibility of Health Departments for Oral Hygiene New York City. Dental Centennial, December 4, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 385)
  - Testimonial Dinner for George H. Whipple, M.D. - Rochester, N.Y., January 15, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 386)
  - Tompkins County Medical Society Meeting. Ithaca, January 23, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 387)
  - Can the Venereal Diseases be Controlled? New York City. Women's City Club, February 21, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 388)
  - Children's Camps - State Supervision New York City. Children's Welfare Federation, March 26, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 389)
  - Public Health Aspects of Syphilis, New York City. University and Bellevue Hospital Medical College, April 16, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 390)
  - The Biggs Memorial Lecture, New York City. Reprints, news releases. New York Academy of Medicine, May 2, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 391)
  - The Biggs Memorial Lecture Correspondence regarding, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 392)
  - Mother' B Day - Maternal Mortality, New York City. New York Maternity Center Association. Meeting was held in Seventh Regiment Armory, May 12, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 393)
  - Municipal Health Problems, Syracuse, N.Y. Mayors Conference, June 5, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 394)
  - The State's Responsibility in Certified Milk, Atlantic City. Meeting of the American Association Medical Milk Commissions, June 11, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 395)
  - Syphilis Problem in New York State -- Correspondence in re. Budapest, Hungary. IX International Dermatological Congress, September 15-21, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 396)
  - Syphilis Problem Reprints, news releases, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 397)
  - Tuberculosis Control in New York State, Official and Non-official Cooperation. Paper read at the annual meeting of the National Tuberculosis Association, Saranoe Lake, N.Y., June, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 398)
  - Prevalence of syphilis and gonorrhea, Upstate New York, 1932-35 (Box 35, Folder 399)
  - Christmas Seal Sale, 1933-1935 (Box 35, Folder 400)
  - Objectives for Hospitals - (Modern Hospital), 1936 (Box 35, Folder 401)
  - Health Security Reprints News releases Folder 1 and 2, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 402-403)
  - Public Health Control of Syphilis - Bibliography file - Detroit, American College of Physicians, March 3, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 404)
  - Ideal Public Health Program - Chicago, Council of Social Agencies. Bibliography files, March 2, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 405)
  - Modern Trends in Public Health, April 1936 (Box 35, Folder 406)
  - The Next Achievement in Public Health. Alabama State Medical Society, Montgomery, April 22, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 407)
  - Expanding Frontiers of Health (Broadcast - N.Y. Med. Society - WABC New York City, April 29, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 408)
  - Prologues - Commencement address, University of Kentucky, Lexington (Box 35, Folder 409)
  - Health Officer's Conference, Louisville, KY, June 4, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 410)
  - Voluntary Services an Essential in a National Health Program, presented at Washington Conference Mobilization for Human Needs, Sept. 18, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 411)
  - Public Health Today Address given at International Medical Assembly of Inter-State Graduate Association, St. Paul, Oct. 14, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 412)
  - Reporting Progress - Dr. Parran's presidential address, American Public Health Association meeting, New Orleans, October 20, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 413)
  - Society for Research in Child Development, Washington, D.C., October 31, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 414)
  - Future Trends in Public Health; Syphilis as a Public Health Problem, Lansing Detroit, November, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 415)
  - James M. Anders Lecture College of Physicians, Philadelphia, November 4, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 416)
  - Smith-Reed-Russell Lecture George Washington University, School of Medicine, December 15, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 417)
  - Delaware Tuberculosis Society Meeting, December 8, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 418)
  - A.M.A. - Presidents and Secretaries of Constituent Associations, Chicago, November 16, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 419)
  - Southern Medical Association, November 1936 (Box 36, Folder 420)
  - Rochester Chamber of Commerce, Rochester, Dec. 2, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 421)
  - Objectives for Hospitals, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 422)
  - Pennsylvania Conference on Social Work Philadelphia, January 18-23, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 423)
  - Farm and Home Week Ithaca, N.Y., Feb 18, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 424)
  - College of Pharmacy and Science Philadelphia, Feb. 23, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 425)
  - American Legion and Cleveland Health Council, Lag in Public Health Consciousness Cleveland, March 15, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 426)
  - German Lectures University of Illinois, March 22-24, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 427)
  - Instructive Visiting Nurse Society Washington, D.C., April 6, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 428)
  - "Public Health Aspects of Syphilis" American College of Physicians St. Louis, April 19-23, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 429)
  - Next Steps in Public Health Tennessee Federation of Women's Clubs, Chattanooga, April 21, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 430)
  - What Can the Private Physician do to Aid in the Control of syphilis? Atlantic City, April 27, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 431)
  - Modern Problems of Child Health National Congress of Parents and Teachers, Richmond, Va., May 4, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 432)
  - Impediments to Maternal Health Maternity Center Association, May 6, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 433)
  - Public Health Aspects of Stream Pollution Washington, D.C., April 26, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 434)
  - Public Health Control of Syphilis- Oklahoma State Medical Society, May 12, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 435)
  - Public Health Control of Syphilis- Texas State Medical Association, Fort Worth, May 13, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 436)
  - Public Health Control of Syphilis- West Virginia State Medical Society, May 26, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 437)
  - Association of American Railroads, Medical and Surgical Section Atlantic City, June 7, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 438)
  - Present Needs in Public Health Control of Gonorrhea. American Meisserian Medical Society, June 8, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 439)
  - Control of Syphilis American Medical Association, Atlantic City, June 9-11, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 440)
  - Headliner's Club, Atlantic City, July 10, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 441)
  - Next Steps in Public Health American Dental Association, Atlantic City, July 13, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 442)
  - Rocky Mountain Medical Conference Denver, July 19-21, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 443)
  - Glenn Dale Sanatorium Washington, D.C., Sept. 15, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 444)
  - The Medical Profession vs. Syphilis, Michigan State Medical Society, September 29, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 445)
  - Snow, William F. - Testimonial Dinner New York, October 1, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 446)
  - National Organization for Public Health Nursing Jubilee Dinner New York, October 4, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 447)
  - Syphilis and Our Children New York Herald - Tribune Forum, October 4, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 448)
  - Syphilis Control Virginia State Medical Society, October 13, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 449)
  - Omaha Mid-West Clinical Society, October 18-22, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 450)
  - Radio script - Y.M.C.A. (Syphilis), October 21, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 451)
  - Education and Syphilis Parent-Teacher Association, Baltimore, October 25, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 452)
  - Syphilis Tri-State Medical Society, Shreveport, La., October 28, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 453)
  - Conference of Mayors Washington, D.C., November 15, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 454)
  - Current Opportunities for Life Conservation Association of Life Insurance Presidents, New York, December 2, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 455)
  - Public Health and Public Welfare American Public Welfare Association, December 10, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 456)
  - Syphilis Control as a Problems of Technology and Economics Cooperative Committee, December 20, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 457)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science Indianapolis, December 20, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 458)
  - Summary - The Health of the South (Box 37, Folder 459)
  - Council of Women and Council of Social Agencies Indianapolis, January 4, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 460)
  - Infantile Paralysis Broadcast, January 21, 1938 (W.R.C.) (Box 37, Folder 461)
  - Indiana State Medical Association, February 7, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 462)
  - Trends in Public Health American College of Physicians, New York, April 4-8, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 463)
  - Relationship of Maternal and Child Health to the General Health Program. Children Bureau Conference, January 17-18, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 464)
  - Columbia University, Institute of Arts and Sciences, January 31, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 465)
  - Social Hygiene Day, February 2, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 466)
  - A Forward Look at National Health Nashville, February 3, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 467)
  - Looking Forward in Public Health Philadelphia Forum, February 11, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 468)
  - Senate Award Northeast High School, Philadelphia, February 11, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 469)
  - Parents Magazine Award NBC Blue Network New York (Box 38, Folder 470)
  - Wisdom and Health General Federation of Women's Clubs N.B.C. (Box 38, Folder 471)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce, February 23, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 472)
  - Forward Look at National Health Delta Omega Society, March 1, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 473)
  - Statement by Surgeon General to Special Senate Committee to Investigate Unemployment and Relief, March 16, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 474)
  - Cancer Broadcast The Mass Attack on Cancer - N.B.C. - 25th Anniversary, American Society for Control of Cancer, March 26, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 475)
  - Syphilis: Health at the Bottom of the Ladder - address Survey Associates, Inc., March 28, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 476)
  - New York County Medical Society, March 28, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 477)
  - "No Defense" Survey-Graphic, April, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 478)
  - Tuberculosis broadcast National Tuberculosis Association, April 5, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 479)
  - State Medical Association Atlantic City, N.J., April 27, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 480)
  - Congress of American Physicians and Surgeons, Atlantic City, May 3-4, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 481)
  - Work and the Aims of the United States Public Health Service Association of American Physicians, Atlantic City, May 4-5, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 482)
  - Medical Profession and Syphilis Philadelphia County Medical Society (Box 38, Folder 483)
  - General Health Council Pittsburgh, May 12, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 484)
  - Syphilis May Be Stamped Out Beaver Falls, Pa., May 12, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 485)
  - A Forward Look at National Health General Federation of Womens' Clubs, Kansas City, May 13, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 486)
  - Missouri Public Health Association Jefferson City, Missouri, May 14, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 487)
  - March of Time talk, May 14, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 488)
  - The Work and Aims of the U.S.P.H.S. Massachusetts Medical Societies, May 31, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 489)
  - Telephone talk Kaufmann's Dept. Store, Pittsburgh, June 1, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 490)